https://www.maddenguides.com/privacy-policy/

your password
Forgot your password?
your email
A password will be e-mailed to you.
Privacy Policy
The information contained in this website is for general information purposes only. The information is provided by Madden Guides.com and while we endeavor to keep the information up to date and correct, we make no representations or warranties of any kind, express or implied, about the completeness, accuracy, reliability, suitability or availability with respect to the website or the information, products, services, or related graphics contained on the website for any purpose. Any reliance you place on such information is therefore strictly at your own risk.
In no event will we be liable for any loss or damage including without limitation, indirect or consequential loss or damage, or any loss or damage whatsoever arising from loss of data or profits arising out of, or in connection with, the use of this website.
Through this website you are able to link to other websites which are not under the control of Madden Guides. We have no control over the nature, content and availability of those sites. The inclusion of any links does not necessarily imply a recommendation or endorse the views expressed within them.
Madden Guides is not associated with the NFL, NFLPA, NCAA, Electronic Arts, or their licensors.
Every effort is made to keep the website up and running smoothly. However, Madden Guides all takes no responsibility for, and will not be liable for, the website being temporarily unavailable due to technical issues beyond our control.
What personal data we collect and why we collect it
When visitors leave comments on the site we collect the data shown in the comments form, and also the visitor’s IP address and browser user agent string to help spam detection.
An anonymized string created from your email address (also called a hash) may be provided to the Gravatar service to see if you are using it. The Gravatar service privacy policy is available here: https://automattic.com/privacy/. After approval of your comment, your profile picture is visible to the public in the context of your comment.
Media
If you upload images to the website, you should avoid uploading images with embedded location data (EXIF GPS) included. Visitors to the website can download and extract any location data from images on the website.
Contact forms
Contact forms are solely used to contact us at Madden Guides.
Cookies
If you leave a comment on our site you may opt-in to saving your name, email address and website in cookies. These are for your convenience so that you do not have to fill in your details again when you leave another comment. These cookies will last for one year.
If you have an account and you log in to this site, we will set a temporary cookie to determine if your browser accepts cookies. This cookie contains no personal data and is discarded when you close your browser.
When you log in, we will also set up several cookies to save your login information and your screen display choices. Login cookies last for two days, and screen options cookies last for a year. If you select “Remember Me”, your login will persist for two weeks. If you log out of your account, the login cookies will be removed.
If you edit or publish an article, an additional cookie will be saved in your browser. This cookie includes no personal data and simply indicates the post ID of the article you just edited. It expires after 1 day.
Embedded content from other websites
Articles on this site may include embedded content (e.g. videos, images, articles, etc.). Embedded content from other websites behaves in the exact same way as if the visitor has visited the other website.
These websites may collect data about you, use cookies, embed additional third-party tracking, and monitor your interaction with that embedded content, including tracing your interaction with the embedded content if you have an account and are logged in to that website.
Who we share your data with
We do not share data with anyone.
How long we retain your data
If you leave a comment, the comment and its metadata are retained indefinitely. This is so we can recognize and approve any follow-up comments automatically instead of holding them in a moderation queue.
For users that register on our website (if any), we also store the personal information they provide in their user profile. All users can see, edit, or delete their personal information at any time (except they cannot change their username). Website administrators can also see and edit that information.
What rights you have over your data
If you have an account on this site, or have left comments, you can request to receive an exported file of the personal data we hold about you, including any data you have provided to us. You can also request that we erase any personal data we hold about you. This does not include any data we are obliged to keep for administrative, legal, or security purposes.
Where we send your data
Visitor comments may be checked through an automated spam detection service.
Your contact information
We do not contact info with anyone.
Thanks,
Madden Guides Staff
RECENT COMMENTSMG Staff on I-Form Slot Flex – PA DaggerMichael Robertson on I-Form Slot Flex – PA DaggerDroopy34 on 4-3 Over – Fire Zone 2Fin on Gun Empty Base Flex – Hoss Y JukeMG Staff on Pass Protection SchemesShopmaster on Pass Protection SchemesKobra on Pass Protection Schemes
Other Madden Sites American Football Monthly
Complete4Ever
Madden University
Operation Sports
Smart Football
Tagsblitz
bump-n-run man beaters
defense
zones
We provide the latest Madden Tips, Madden Strategies, Madden Formations, Madden Plays, Madden News, and Madden Videos.Contact us: info@maddenguides.com
EVEN MORE NEWS
Quick Passing Game – Attacking the Flats
December 10, 2020
Singleback Deuce Close – PA X Post Cross
December 9, 2020
Gun Doubles Flex Bills – Bills Corner
December 9, 2020
POPULAR CATEGORYMadden Plays41Madden Tips31Madden Tools27Madden Playbooks14Madden Strategies9Madden Formations8News5
© 2020 Madden Guides. Madden Guides is not affiliated or associated with EA Sports, the NFL, or their license.
error:
